we've got the donuts we've got the
我们有甜甜圈 我们有甜甜圈
animation now it's time to do our final
动画现在是我们最后一场比赛的时候了
lovely
可爱的
render so we are rendering using the
渲染 因此我们使用
Cycles rendering engine which to jog
循环要慢跑的渲染引擎
your memory from the uh rendering video
你对渲染视频的记忆
the way it works is turning off D noise
它的工作方式是关闭D噪波
is it starts with a very noisy image
它是从一个非常嘈杂的图像开始的吗
with a low sample count and then over
样本计数较低 然后结束
time you can see in the top left there
你可以在左上角看到的时间
it throws more samples at it and it
它向它扔更多的样本 然后它
refines that image to be uh cleaner and
将图像提炼得更干净
cleaner essentially so if we were to set
基本上更干净了 如果我们要设置
this uh maximum sample count to a really
这个 呃 最大样本计数真的是
absurdly low value like say 10 samples
低得离谱 比如10个样品
you can see it renders very quickly
您可以看到它渲染得非常快
right it's done almost instantaneously
是的 它几乎是在瞬间完成的
but it's so noisy that you can't see any
但它太吵了 你看不见任何东西
of the detail now there is the magical D
在细节中 现在有了神奇的D
noise function which we will be using
我们将使用的噪声函数
however that is not it it does solve a
然而 这不是它 它确实解决了一个
lot it's definitely definitely helpful
洛特 这绝对是有帮助的
but it's not perfect especially for
但它并不完美 特别是对于
animations because on each frame the
动画 因为在每一帧上
sample variation um even though it's set
样本变化嗯 即使它是设定的
to be stable um there will be variances
为了稳定 嗯 会有变化的
frameo frame so if you're using a low
帧 所以如果你使用的是低音
sample count this Aid noiser it will do
样品计数这个辅助噪音音响可以用
its best but it'll still have like
这是最好的 但还是会有这样的
splotchy patterns that will appear and
将出现的斑驳图案和
you can actually notice it if you go
如果你去的话 你实际上可以注意到它
looking for it um like the other day I
寻找它 嗯 就像前几天我
was watching one of uh Mr BEAST's videos
在看比斯特先生的一段视频
and there was like an animation in it
里面有一部动画片
and I was looking at and I saw like all
我看着 我看到了所有的
this splotchy stuff like in on the sides
这个污点的东西就像在边上
and I was like oh damn that must be on
我当时想 哦 该死的 那一定是开着的
like a really tight deadline cuz they
就像一个非常紧迫的最后期限 因为他们
did not have time to render out uh the
没有时间来呈现呃
proper the proper samples um but anyways
适当的样品嗯但不管怎样
so I did a few tests for this exact
所以我为这个做了几个测试
scene here um you can see this is with
这里的场景嗯 你可以看到这是
20 samples you zoom into the background
放大背景的20个样本
there you can see splotchiness it's um
在那里你可以看到斑点 它是嗯
especially noticeable in out of focus
尤其是在《失焦》中
areas which I'll show you how to do that
我将向您展示如何做到这一点
out of focusness soon um but you can see
很快就会变得模糊 但你可以看到
it's very splotchy and you wouldn't ever
这是非常脏的 你永远不会
want to use it 50 starts to look a
想要用它50岁开始看起来
little more stable but still the
稍微稳定一些 但仍然是
splotchiness is very noticeable you
你身上的污点很明显
don't want that 100 this is where it's
我不想要那100美元 这就是它
starting to look usable but still not
开始看起来有用 但仍然不是
great I wouldn't consider that good 300
太好了 我不认为那是好的300
samples is where I consider the uh the
样品是我认为 呃
bare minimum for a scene like this but
对于这样的场景来说是最低限度的 但是
ideally you would be able to go up to
理想情况下 你将能够达到
500 samples which is where a lot of that
500个样品 这是其中很大一部分
splotchiness is so negligible that you
污点是如此微不足道 以至于你
don't really notice it and if you have
不要真的注意到它 如果你有
time or you don't mind rendering you
时间或者你不介意把你
know overnight or something like that or
一夜之间或诸如此类的事
maybe a couple of overnights a thousand
也许是几个过夜 一千个
samples will get you an even cleaner
样品会让你变得更干净
looking result so for my Max sample
为我的最大样本寻找结果
amount I'm going to go with 500 and by
我要用500美元 然后
the way there is viewport and there is
有了视窗 就有了
render and these settings are identical
渲染和这些设置是相同的
um I was tweaking viewport before
嗯 我之前在调整视窗
because I was showing you uh in the
因为我是在给你展示 呃 在
viewport but obviously it's what's in
视窗 但很明显它是里面的东西
the render settings which is going to be
渲染设置将是
saved into your final uh animation there
保存到您最后的呃动画中
is also noise threshold also known as
噪声阈值也称为
adaptive sampling and the way this works
自适应采样及其工作方式
is it will try to look at the image and
它会试着看这张图片
determine which areas are already clean
确定哪些区域已经清洁
enough and then which areas need more
足够了 然后哪些领域需要更多
samples like dark areas where there's
样本喜欢黑暗的区域 那里有
not enough light or something and it'll
光线不够之类的 它就会
throw more samples specifically into
把更多的样本明确地扔到
that area and it's very efficient and I
那个区域 非常高效 我
would love to use it unfortunately it
我很想用它不幸的是
doesn't play well with the denoiser with
与消噪器配合得不太好
the denoiser it can create splotchy
它可以产生污点的消噪效果
areas which are not good obviously so if
显然不是很好的领域如果
you're using the denoiser which let's
您使用的是去噪器 它让我们
face it is probably 99% of the time then
面对面 那可能是99%的时间
you can't really use the noise Threshold
你不能真的使用噪音阈值
at least as far as I've seen I haven't
至少在我看来我还没有
seen it work uh reliably enough so
看到它的工作 呃 足够可靠
uncheck noise threshold samples I went
取消选中我去过的噪波阈值样本
with 500 try to go yeah if you're on a
有500个人试着去是的如果你在
laptop maybe 300 but try to go uh up
笔记本电脑可能是300台 但要试着往上
from there and you'll get a nice a clean
从那里 你会得到一个很好的清洁
result there's also time limit I almost
结果也有时间限制 我几乎
never use this but this just puts like a
永远不要用这个 但这只会让你觉得
cap on each frame so if I don't know the
在每一帧上加盖 所以如果我不知道
samples was going to take the image like
样本将会像这样拍摄图像
25 seconds to render if you set your
25秒来呈现 如果您设置
your time limit to be 20 seconds it
你的时间限制是20秒吗
would just stop at whatever uh sample
会停在任何 呃 样品上
count 20 seconds gives it and then it
倒数20秒给它 然后它
would move on to the next frame but as I
会转移到下一帧 但当我
said I almost never use it I just want
我说我几乎从不用它 我只是想
to use the exact sample count awesome
用精确的样本计数来说真是太棒了
now you might remember previously um
现在你可能还记得之前的这个
that when you want to do a render you go
当您想要进行渲染时 您可以
render render image or you hit F12 and
渲染渲染图像或按F12和
then this will kick off a single still
然后这将开始一台单人蒸馏器
render and then from here if I wanted to
渲染 然后从这里 如果我想要
save this image I would go image save as
保存此图像我会将图像另存为
well what we want to do is we want to
我们想做的是我们想要
render a sequence like a you know as
呈现一个序列 如您所知的
every single frame um and so to do that
每一帧 嗯 然后这样做
we want to use not just render but
我们不仅要使用渲染 还要使用
render
渲染
animation and when you do that it will
动画 当你这样做的时候 它将
use and it will save the file for you in
使用 它将为您将文件保存在
whatever you put in the output settings
无论您在输出设置中设置了什么
over here so if we bring this out over
在这里 所以如果我们把这个拿出来
here uh you can see your resolutions
在这里 呃 你可以看到你的决心
defined up there you got your frame rate
在那里定义 你得到你的帧速率
yada yada the output one here so this is
呀 这里是输出的 所以这是
the folder where it's going to save the
它将在其中保存
file to and then your file format I'll
文件到 然后你的文件格式 我会
just move this up um this is a really
把这个往上移 嗯 这真的是
important one now you would think that
现在你会认为这是一个重要的问题
because we want to create a video file
因为我们要创建一个视频文件
right that you could upload to Instagram
对 你可以上传到Instagram
or YouTube or whatever that you would
或YouTube或任何你想要的东西
want to use one of these movie settings
我想要使用以下电影设置之一
maybe an AVI or an FFM Peg or something
可能是AVI或FFM钉或其他什么
like that
就像这样
but you would not you would be wrong but
但你不会你会错的但是
it's a common uh mistake a lot of
这是一个常见的 呃 很多错误
beginners make the reason you don't want
初学者说出你不想要的理由
to ever ever render a scene directly
曾经直接渲染场景
into this format is that if if at any
转换成这种格式的是 如果有
point during the uh rendering process
在呃渲染过程中的点
your computer was to crash or let's face
你的电脑要死机了 要不我们来面对
it Windows was to do another update
IT Windows本来要进行另一次更新
overnight and you can never figure out
一夜之间 你永远也想不出
when it's going to do it and it just
当它要这么做的时候 它只是
does it randomly and you anyways uh if
它是随机的吗？不管怎么说 如果
it was to do that you would lose
如果你这样做 你会输的
everything everything you have rendered
你所呈现的一切
has just vanished because it will not
已经消失了 因为它不会
have created any file that you can
我已经创建了您可以创建的任何文件
actually read so instead you always
实际上读起来 所以你总是
render to still images okay so you want
渲染到静止图像可以 因此您希望
every single one of these frames to
这些帧中的每一个都要
create a PNG and then put it into the
创建一个PNG 然后将其放入
output folder there which you will then
输出文件夹 然后您将在其中
later take that sequence of 300 PNG
稍后再取300个PNG序列
images let's say or it's 160 in this
图片 比方说 这里面有160张
case um and then put that into another
箱子嗯 然后放到另一个箱子里
process which I'll show you to uh to
过程 我会带你去 呃 去
create that final video file so PNG is
创建最终的视频文件 以便PNG
actually pretty good for most cases uh
实际上对大多数情况来说都很好 嗯
if you want to go a slightly higher
如果您想再高一点的话
quality you could use Tiff if you really
质量您可以使用Tiff 如果您真的
know what you're doing you could use
知道你在做什么你可以利用
open exr but the problem with that is
打开EXR 但它的问题是
that it will not use uh it won't embed
它不会使用 呃它不会嵌入
like a display uh transform in it so
就像一个展示 呃 在里面变换一下
it'll save it into linear format
它会将其保存为线性格式
technical jargon just to say it's going
技术术语只是为了说它正在进行
to look terrible if you don't know what
如果你不知道什么会让你看起来很可怕
you're doing with it so generally
你用它做的太笼统了
speaking uh PNG or or Tiff is the one
说 呃 PNG或或Tiff是一个
you want never jpeg the compression on
你想永远不要打开jpeg压缩
that is terrible unless you're just you
这太可怕了 除非你只是你
know throwing a still image up on
知道在上面放一张静止的图片
Facebook or something uh but PNG or Tiff
Facebook之类的 但是PNG或Tiff
that's fine and the color depth uh you
很好 而且颜色深度 呃 你
could go8 or 16 bits 16 bits will give
可以得到8位或16位16位将给出
you a lot more range but it will be
你的范围要大得多 但它会
larger files um unless you're planning
更大的文件 嗯 除非您计划
to do color grading and something like
来做颜色分级之类的事情
after effect or nuke or something I
后遗症或核武器或其他什么我
wouldn't bother with 16bit 8 should be
不会为16位8应该是
fine so you set your output folder to be
很好 所以您将输出文件夹设置为
something that makes sense I usually
一些有意义的事情我通常
just create a folder called uh frames uh
只需创建一个名为呃Frame的文件夹
and then within here I just create
然后在这里 我创造了
another sub folder I call it like one um
另一个子文件夹 我叫它 就像一个
just because you almost always need to
仅仅因为你几乎总是需要
render multiple times but anyways you
渲染多次 但无论如何
you you create a sub folder there called
您可以在那里创建一个名为
one um and then yeah I just kick off uh
一个 嗯 然后是的 我只是开始 嗯
the render by going render animation but
通过使用渲染动画进行渲染 但
before you do that it is a good idea to
在此之前 最好先
check your scene to make sure that you
检查你的场景 确保你
haven't got any mistakes because you're
没有任何错误 因为你是
going to be rendering and usually you're
会被渲染 通常你会
rendering overnight or maybe a sequence
整夜渲染或可能是一系列渲染
of days and you don't want to have to go
几天 你不会想去
through the whole process of rendering
通过渲染的整个过程
only to bring it up and then go like oh
只是把它举起来 然后就像这样
crap I forgot to turn on that layer or I
糟了 我忘了打开那个层了 不然我
forgot to fix that problem or I didn't
忘了解决那个问题 或者我没有
notice this before I did the render and
在我进行渲染之前 请注意这一点
then you have to do the whole thing all
那你就得把所有的事都做完
over again so here's a checklist first
再来一遍 这是第一张清单
in solid View mode click this little
在Solid View模式下 单击此小
drop down next to your viewport overlays
在您的视区叠加旁边的下拉列表
and then go face orientation now what
然后去面对面 现在怎么办？
this is showing you is which faces are
这是在向你展示哪些脸是
facing the correct direction so the face
面对正确的方向 这样的脸
is the solid part of the mesh and it's
是网格的实体部分 它是
like paper thin right but there is a
像纸一样薄 对吧 但有一个
correct direction and there is a wrong
正确的方向就有错误的方向
direction so the correct direction is is
方向 所以正确的方向是
the direction that the the camera and
摄像机和摄像机的方向
the Shader expects to see and it can
着色器期望看到 它可以看到
render correctly if it's showing you the
如果它向您显示
opposite side of the face it means that
脸的对立面 意思是
the shading is likely to get screwed up
阴影很可能会弄乱
so if you see anything in your scene
所以如果你在你的场景中看到任何东西
that is red it means that it is facing
那是红色的 表示它正对着
the wrong direction okay so in this case
方向不对 所以在这种情况下
it thought that the kitchen should be
它认为厨房应该是
rendered outside right because it was a
在右侧呈现 因为它是一个
cube that we started with so it puts the
我们一开始使用的立方体 所以它将
faces outside it cuz it wouldn't know
外面的脸 因为它不会知道
that we want to render inside it so in
我们想要在它里面渲染的
this case if you have a red face like
这种情况下 如果你有一张红脸 比如
this you select it select everything on
这是您选择的选项 选择所有选项
the mesh just by tapping a and then you
只需轻拍一个网格 然后您就可以
want to hit shift n okay now that should
想按下Shift n键吗？好的 现在应该可以了
fix it if it doesn't because on the case
如果不是就修好它 因为在这个案子上
you want to have it facing uh inwards
你想让它朝向 呃 向内
like in this case uh this little
就像在这种情况下 呃 这个小
recalculate normals box here if you
如果您要重新计算法线 请在此处
click that you can then click the check
单击 然后您可以单击选中
boox that says inside or a hotkey for it
布克斯 里面写着 还是热键
is control shiftn and that will do a
是控制权转移 这将会做一个
recalculation uh inside anyways long
再算一遍吧 反正里面很长
story short you just want to make sure
简而言之 你只是想确保
that everything you see is blue if
如果你看到的一切都是蓝色的
you've got anything a Sprinkle or you
你有没有什么东西是撒的或者你
know a donut or a plate or anything like
知道甜甜圈或盘子或任何类似的东西
that just make sure everything is
那只是要确保一切都
showing up as blue um because that's
显示为蓝色 嗯 因为那是
very important all right so now that's
非常重要 好的 现在这是
done I can turn that off the other thing
好了 我可以把另一件事关掉
that you want to check is that you
你想要检查的是你
haven't got any Rogue uh objects that
没有任何无赖 呃 物品
will be showing up in the render that
将在渲染中显示
you don't want to be there like for
你不会想呆在那里 就像
example this weird looking little UFO
例如 这个看起来很奇怪的小UFO
thing right these little sprinkles that
正确的事情这些小点点
are just hovering off into space here so
只是在太空中徘徊 所以
that is because we've got some sprinkles
那是因为我们有一些点缀
which are being referenced on our
它们在我们的
geometry node stack but we don't want
几何节点堆栈 但我们不希望
these individual ones which are being
这些个体正在成为
referenced to appear in the render so on
引用以显示在渲染中等
the sprinkles collection I'm just going
Sinkles系列我正要去
to uncheck this little camera icon and
取消选中此小相机图标并
that means it's viewable in the viewport
这意味着它在视口中可见
but it's not going to appear in the
但它不会出现在
render this will not affect the objects
渲染此操作不会影响对象
over here when it's referenced in a
在这里 当它在
geometry node system it's just going to
几何节点系统 它只是要
treat that as its own separate thing and
把它当做它自己的独立事物
it's not going to uh hide it from the
它不会呃把它藏起来不让
render but it just means that these five
渲染 但这只意味着这五个
little reference sprinkles will be
小的参考喷洒将是
invisible in the render the other thing
在渲染中不可见的另一个对象
that you want to check is is to look at
你想要检查的是
your intersections okay because looking
你的交叉口没问题是因为看起来
at my donut look at that wow I've got a
在我的甜甜圈上看着那个哇我有一个
massive intersection and this would be
巨大的十字路口 这将是
noticeable because the camera is now
值得注意的是因为摄像机现在
moving and it is above it right so you
移动 它就在它的正上方 所以你
don't want to have uh intersections so
我不想有交叉路口 所以
I'm actually going to use this as an
我实际上要把这当作一种
excuse to uh slightly reorient um my
借口 呃 稍微改变一下我的方向
donuts and create a much more appealing
甜甜圈和创造一个更有吸引力的
looking stack cuz I was experimenting
看着堆栈是因为我在做实验
before I hit the record button and I
在我按下录音按钮之前 我
thought if I just create you know both
我想如果我只是创造你两者都知道
of these stacks so they're kind of like
这些堆栈 所以它们有点像
leaning on each other then I rotate them
相互倚靠 然后我旋转它们
a little bit like this then I take this
有点像这样 然后我拿着这个
donut I could move it out rotate
甜甜圈 我可以把它轮流搬出去
that something like
这就像是
this there we go right and then oh
在这里 我们向右 然后哦
yeah I'll rotate this a little bit more
好的 我会把这个再旋转一点
it's a leaning tower of
它是一座斜塔
Donuts I'll move that out a little
甜甜圈 我要把它挪开一点
bit but really with this many many
有点 但真的有这么多
objects on top of each other you're
物体堆积在一起 你是
bound to have something that looks a
一定会有一些看起来像是
little funky so just look at it from
有点时髦 所以就从
different angles I mean the most
不同的角度 我是说最多的
important one is the camera right making
重要的一点是相机的正确制作
sure that it is uh sensible but because
当然 呃 这是明智的 但因为
we've got a moving camera it kind of has
我们有一个移动的摄像头 它有点像
to look good from multiple angles um the
从多个角度看起来都很好
other thing I noticed also is uh it
我注意到的另外一件事呢也是
would look a lot better if I could see
如果我能看到的话会好很多
the top of this dut here so I noticed if
这块灰尘的顶部 所以我注意到
I select this stack and I rotate it like
我选择这个堆栈 然后像这样旋转它
this almost like it's on the edge of
这几乎就像是在
that plate there like the lip and it's
那个盘子就像嘴唇 它是
kind of leaning this way it looks a lot
有点向这边倾斜 它看起来很大
nicer yeah see now I can see the top of
更好了 是啊 现在我可以看到
that donut and uh yeah just feels a lot
那个甜甜圈 呃 是的 只是感觉很多
nicer might actually rotate a little bit
更好的人实际上可能会旋转一点
further and then I'll move it
再远一点 然后我就把它移走
up rotate this
向上旋转这个
one I'll pull that in a little
一 我会把它拉进去一点
bit and that's pretty good that's not
比特 这很好 不是
bad all right there so that's a lot more
坏的 好的 所以这是更多的
interesting and I've also corrected a
有趣的是 我还更正了一个
lot of the inter sections there but you
除了你 还有很多不同的人
know as I mentioned before guys this is
就像我之前提到的 伙计们 这是
a tutorial and I can't fix everything
一本教程 我不可能解决所有问题
whilst I'm uh running the tutorial so uh
当我 呃 运行教程的时候 所以
have a look at your scene and have a
看一看你的现场 并有一个
look at you know the plate is there a
看 你知道车牌在那里吗？
doughnut which is hovering above the
在空中盘旋的甜甜圈
plate like it is here make sure that
像这样的盘子一定要确保
it's not or at least make sure that it
它不是 或者至少确保它
is not in a place that's noticeable um
不在一个明显的地方 嗯
because that will not be good and you'll
因为这不是好事 你会
be on I mean I actually finished the
我是说我真的完成了
final animation sequence uh for this
最终的动画序列呢就是这个
tutorial and then notice right at the
教程 然后请注意
end uh that one of the donuts was like
结束 呃 其中一个甜甜圈是这样的
this and I just didn't notice it right
我只是没有注意到这一点
until I did uh after the uh the render
直到我做了 呃 在渲染之后
sequence was complete and actually a
序列是完整的 实际上是一个
co-worker of mine was also working on
我的一位同事也在研究
the scene helping render some uh extra
这个场景帮助渲染了一些呃额外的东西
sequences and he didn't notice it either
序列 他也没有注意到
and we're both like damn how did we miss
我们都像是该死的我们怎么会错过
that cuz you just don't go looking for
因为你不会去寻找
it so I'm calling it out now cuz I'm
所以我现在就喊出来 因为我是
sure a lot of you watching have got
当然 你们中的许多人都有
intersections and uh it's good to try to
十字路口 呃 试着去
fix it now another one to check for is
现在修复它另一个需要检查的是
your lighting and your Expos exposure
您的灯光和世博会曝光率
ranges so first thing I know is that
所以我知道的第一件事就是
looking at this is this is good it's
看着这个 这很好 这是
putting a lot of the attention on the
把大量的注意力放在
donuts which is great but this uh
甜甜圈 这很棒 但是这个 呃
everything here in the background is
背景中的一切都是
just it's so dark it's almost hard to
只是天太黑了 几乎很难
see and it feels a little bit too moody
你看 感觉有点太情绪化了
right it's almost like a Rembrant uh
对 几乎就像一幅伦勃朗 嗯
painting or something like that I want
我想要画画或类似的东西
it to feel a little lighter a little bit
感觉轻松了一点
more uh friendly so on the roof here on
更友好 所以在屋顶上
the ceiling of my kitchen I'm going to
我要去厨房的天花板
shift and then right click to put my 3
按住Shift 然后单击鼠标右键将我的3
cursor there and then right at that
光标在那里 然后就在那里
point I'm going to add in an area lamp
我要加上一盏区域灯
and I'm just going to move it down
我要把它往下移
slightly just to make sure it's not
只是为了确保它不会
clipping through the surface um and then
穿过表面 然后
yeah let's go look in this so this is
好的 我们去看看这个 这是
what it is with it off and then if I
脱掉它是什么 然后如果我
just increase this you can see it's just
只要增加这个 你就会看到 它只是
adding a little bit of fill light to the
将一点填充光添加到
whole scene to just feel a little bit
整个场景只是感觉到一点
lighter um and a little less uh yeah
轻一点 嗯 少一点 嗯 是的
extreme in its uh light choice but yeah
在它的 呃 轻便的选择上是极端的 但是的
that looks pretty good now by the way
顺便说一句 现在看起来很不错
this power value there's something
这个功率值有一些东西
called the inverse Square law that
称为平方反比定律
applies to all lights in the real world
适用于现实世界中的所有灯光
and in 3D software it just means that if
而在3D软件中 这只是意味着如果
something is double like twice as close
有些东西就像是两倍接近
to something it means it's going to be
这意味着它将会是
four times as bright so what this means
四倍的光明 这意味着什么？
is that I've just added in a an area
我刚刚在一个区域中添加了
lamp right at the top of my ceiling but
灯就在我的天花板上 但是
that's because this is just the size of
那是因为这正好是
the box that I've got if yours is a
我有一个盒子 如果你的盒子是
little bit uh shorter than this right
比这个稍微短一点 对吧
then when you placed it then this lamp
然后当你把它放在台灯上的时候
and this lamp energy that we've just
我们刚刚得到的这盏灯的能量
defined here as you know 10 watts it's
这里的定义是10瓦 它是
going to be a lot brighter so don't copy
会更明亮 所以不要照搬
the values that I'm putting here have a
我在这里提出的价值观有一个
look at your scene and try to evaluate
看着你的场景 试着评估
and go is it bright enough is it too
还有 它够亮吗 它也够亮吗
bright do I feel that this fill light is
我是不是觉得这个补光很亮
too overpowering right or is it
太右了还是太右了？
underpowering just evaluate and try to
力不从心只需评估并尝试
do it um as fairly as you can and
尽你所能公平地做 嗯 然后
something that I recommend um and this I
我推荐一些东西 嗯 这个我
do uh a lot of the time for a lot of
做 呃 很多时间 很多时候
final renders is underneath your color
最终渲染效果取决于您的颜色
management if you go to view transform
管理 如果您转到查看转型
change it from agx to false color H now
现在将其从agx更改为假颜色H
this obviously you never want to do for
这显然是你永远不想做的事
a final render but this is revealing to
最终渲染 但这揭示了
you what is the exposure range of
你的暴露范围是多少？
different parts of the image kind of
图像的不同部分就像
like if you're using a camera and it's
例如 如果你使用的是摄像机 而它是
got like a zebra thing to like show you
像斑马一样的东西向你展示
which parts are clipping this is like
哪个部分被修剪了？这就像
that but it's like to an advanced level
但这就像是达到了一个更高的水平
essentially it's showing you I mean I'll
基本上 它是在向你展示我的意思是 我会
put this up from the blender
把这个从搅拌机里拿出来
documentation but it's showing you what
文档 但它向您展示了
is the exposure range of which parts of
是哪部分的曝光范围
the image and there's no like right or
图像 没有类似的权利或
wrong here but generally speaking you
这里错了 但总的来说 你
want to have a nice range because then
想要一个很好的范围 因为
it's showing there are parts that are in
它显示出有一些部件在
light and then there are parts that are
光 然后有一些部件是
in Shadows and there is a range there so
在阴影中 那里有一个范围 所以
that you can reveal the form there are
你可以展示那里的形式
exceptions to it but generally that's
例外情况 但通常情况下
the idea now in my case I want to make
对我来说 我现在想要的想法是
sure that um really there's very few
当然 嗯 真的很少
areas that are in the red or the white
红色或白色区域
the white means there is actually no
白色表示实际上没有
information there because it has clipped
信息在那里 因为它已经剪断了
so that is not good it's okay for a few
所以这不太好 对一些人来说还可以
areas right where there's a few
就在那里有几个
highlights but generally speaking you
重点突出 但总的来说 你
don't want too much now in my case I
我现在不想要太多 对我来说
think it's a little bit too high so I'm
我觉得有点太高了 所以我
just dialing it back and just so that I
只是回拨一下 这样我就可以
get most of you know the part of the
让你们中的大多数人知道
donut where it's hitting the light um
甜甜圈在它击中光线的地方嗯
it's mostly in the orange to Yellow
它主要是在橙色到黄色之间
range with a very small amounts of um
含有非常少量的Um
yeah red or white coming through so once
是啊 红色或白色只有一次
I'm happy with that make sure you change
我对此很满意确保你能改变
it back to agx otherwise you'll be
它回到了AGX 否则你就会
rendering to false color and that will
渲染到错误的颜色 这将
look horrible a few other aesthetic
看起来很可怕 还有一些其他的美学
choices I noticed that the pink was a
选择我注意到粉色是一种
little bit too hot the saturation does
饱和度有点太热了
make a difference so I'm just going to
有所作为 所以我要
dial it back to around about a 6 value I
将其拨回约6的值i
also noticed that this yellow color was
我还注意到这个黄色是
a little bit too close to mustard so I'm
有点太接近芥末了 所以我
just going to tweak the Hue here just to
我要把这里的色调调到
make it a little bit more exciting kind
让它变得更刺激一点
of like a banana yellow right and a
就像香蕉黄的右边和一个
little bit brighter as well just a
也稍微亮一点 只是
little bit more cheerful the blue I'm
忧郁的我更快乐一点
going to make a little closer to an aqua
我要做得更接近水上运动
which is a little more funky a little I
更时髦一点的是我
don't know more interesting at least to
不知道至少更有趣的是
me uh the base color oh yeah this one
我 呃 底色 哦 对了 这件
here so I decided after looking at this
所以我在看了这个之后决定
and evaluating it I'm like I should just
评估一下 我觉得我应该
go with the the white icing like what I
像我一样和白色的糖衣一起走
had in my uh my final render so just
在我的 呃 我最后的演示稿中
creating a new material call it white
创造一种新材质 称之为白色
icing right um and also for the doughnut
加冰对了 还有甜甜圈
I noticed I forgot to put subsurface
我注意到我忘了放在地下
scattering on the doughnut itself um
撒在甜甜圈上
because doughnut although it's bread
因为甜甜圈虽然是面包
right it's not going to have as much
对 它不会有那么多
subsurface scattering as the icing but
次表面散射作为糖衣 但
it will have some right so I'm going to
它会有一些权利 所以我要
give it a weight of one uh radius make
给它一个呃半径的重量
sure that's always set to one and then
当然 它总是设置为1 然后
this value here let's go
这个值在这里 我们开始吧
01 um like that which I think is
01这个就像我想的那样
actually more than the icing we gave it
实际上比我们给它的糖衣更多
but anyways it works because it's kind
但不管怎样 它很管用 因为它很友善
of doughy um we can kind of get away
对于面团 嗯 我们可以离开
maybe maybe we having second thoughts
也许我们要重新考虑一下
right now uh yeah we got Point 01 why
现在 嗯 是的 我们得到了01点为什么
not make it look a little bit more
而不是让它看起来更像
stylized and uh cartoonish the other
风格化和呃卡通化的另一种
thing that I can see looking at this is
看着这个我能看到的是
that this part here right with these
这部分就在这里 还有这些
ball sprinkles on it is it's very like
球撒在上面是因为它很像
high frequency detail which is just like
高频细节 就像
a technical term to mean like small
一个专业术语 意思是像小
detail artists always invent terms just
细节艺术家总是创造出公正的术语
to sound uh smarter than they are but it
听起来 呃 比他们聪明 但是
looks high frequency right and it's a
看起来频率很高 这是一种
little too high frequency it's good to
频率有点太高了 很好
have some small detail but not that
有一些小细节 但不是那个
small it's just uh it's kind of gritty
它很小 只是 呃 它有点粗
and it's kind of like it's sticking out
这就像是它突出了
like a sore thumb to me so what I'm
对我来说就像一个酸痛的拇指 所以我
going to do is go to my geometry nose
我要做的就是去看我的几何鼻子
setup just for my round sprinkles here
只为我的圆形洒水做准备
um and by the way also make sure you
嗯 顺便说一句 你也要确保
you're looking at the correct one not
你看到的是正确的 而不是
long sprinkles uncheck that little pin
长长的喷洒取消勾选那个小别针
if you've got it like I did um and then
如果你像我一样 嗯 然后
I'm going to change the round sprinkle
我要换成圆形的洒水
scale dragging down to
比例向下拖动至
1.5 so it's a lot bigger which means I
1.5所以它要大得多 这意味着我
can use a different distance Min
可以使用不同的最小距离
value
价值
002 and whilst I'm here um I'm also
当我在这里的时候 嗯 我也
going to change the distance value for
要更改的距离值
the long sprinkles cuz I noticed it was
长长的喷雾因为我注意到它是
feeling a little too even the
感觉有点太过了
distribution of these which generally
它们的分布通常是
means that with this pron disc
意味着有了这张PRON盘
distribution it's using the distance to
它使用距离进行分布
make sure they're all perfectly evenly
确保它们都完全均匀
spaced and it's a little bit it's it's
有间隔的 有一点 这是
too big essentially so I'm going to set
本质上太大了 所以我要把
this to 0.4 instead which means you will
改为0.4 这意味着您将
have some overlaps and some clipping but
有一些重叠和一些剪辑 但
if we use a lower count here in our
如果我们在我们的
setup like 80 for example or even lower
例如 设置为80或更低
right it should feel a lot more natural
对 应该感觉自然多了
right it doesn't look like like before
好的 看起来不像以前了
it was like 200 um when it was uh you
当它是呃你的时候 好像是200个
know this was 06 and now it's like 30
我知道这是06 现在大概是30
but it still almost feels like the same
但感觉还是和以前一样
as what it was before because that
就像以前一样 因为
distance when you lower it you're
距离当你降低它的时候 你是
getting more sprinkles in there even
在那里得到更多的洒水
though it's a lower sprinkle density
尽管它的喷洒密度较低
anyways technical uh also lower this one
不管怎样 技术上的 呃 也把这个放低一点
cuz that's just too many so let's go
因为太多了 我们走吧
like 50 for that um and that's pretty
比如50美元 嗯 这很不错
good you can also experiment like I
很好 你也可以像我一样做实验
tried changing the different um um like
我试着把不同的这个像这样
whether this one has long sprinkles or
不管这个有长长的洒水 还是
whether this one at the top has round
上面这张是不是有圆的
you can play around with these I went uh
你可以玩这些我去了呃
I think the bottom one I gave long this
我想我给的最底层的是这个
one I'm going to turn it off so none
一 我要把它关掉 这样就没有
no sprinkles on that one and just try
不要在这上面撒任何东西 试一试
and get a nice you know feel for it
得到一种你知道的美好的感觉
really you're just trying to go for
真的 你只是想要
something that looks a little balanced
看起来有点平衡的东西
in its detail so you don't have too much
在细节上 所以你不会有太多
repetition um across it so I'm trying to
重复它 嗯 所以我试着
get a nice breakup of like round long
好好地分手 就像圆圆的长
nun none round you know Etc the other
修女周围没有你认识的人等另一个人
thing since we're talking about detail
既然我们谈论的是细节
is looking at this right this is small
正看着这个 这是小的
detail this is small detail these shapes
细节这是很小的细节这些形状
here right this is large detail Okay so
这里 这是大细节 好的 那么
we've got large and we've got this small
我们有大的 也有这个小的
detail we don't have any medium detail
细节我们没有任何中等细节
um and it's good to have a variance
嗯 有一个差异是很好的
across the scene just I don't know it's
在整个场景中 我只是不知道它是
one of the design rules it just helps
其中一条设计规则只是帮助
things feel a little bit more
感觉事情会更多一点
aesthetically pleasing so uh something I
在审美上令人愉悦 所以呃 一些我
I saw when I was looking on Pinterest
当我看着Pinterest的时候我看到了
many years ago uh for one of the old
很多年前 呃 对于一位老人来说
Donut series was like uh you can put
甜甜圈系列就像呃你可以把
bigger sprinkles like a few big chunky
更大的洒水 就像几个大块
sprinkles on it and uh it just adds
洒在上面 呃 它只是增加了
variance to it and it just makes it look
对它的不同 它只是让它看起来
a lot more appealing so for that I'm you
更有吸引力 所以我就是你
could do it using geometry nodes but I
我可以使用几何体节点来实现 但我
just do it by hand placing like three
只要用手放在三个位置就可以了
sprinkles so on this donut here shift
所以洒在这个甜甜圈上的班次
right clicking on this part of the donut
右键单击甜甜圈的这一部分
uh I'll go into uh here we go solid View
呃 我要进去 呃 我们来看看实景
mode and then shift a and then I'm going
模式 然后按Shift a键 然后我要
to add in a UV sphere default settings
添加UV球体默认设置
are okay just going to scale it
只要把它放进去就行了吗？
down like that right so this is the size
就像那样 就是这个大小
of the sprinkle quite big you could
洒得很大 你可以
imagine it almost as like a gumball or
把它想象成一个口香糖或者
something um it's probably not big
什么 嗯 可能不是很大
enough to be a gumball but you know what
足够做口香糖了 但你知道吗
I mean like something big right make
我的意思是 像是一些大的正确的事情
sure you're using shade smooth and for
当然 您使用的是Shape Smooth和
the
这个
material um sorry if this is like
材料 嗯 抱歉 如果这就像
getting to in the weeds but a lot of
在杂草丛中 但有很多
people when they're following tutorials
当人们在学习教程时
they like to know the exact settings
他们想知道确切的设置
that I used so I'm trying to show them
我用过 所以我试着向他们展示
all um whilst not taking too long um but
所有的 嗯 虽然不会花太长时间 但是
yeah there we go so I go for like a aqua
是的 我们去了 所以我去喝一杯水
color yeah like that and then I want to
颜色 对 就像这样 然后我想
turn the roughness like like all the way
把粗糙度变得像一路一样
down like that cool and now I just need
如此冷静 现在我只需要
to duplicate that sprinkle so duplicate
把那个洒水复制得如此复制
here uh I'll pull it out and I'm just
在这里 呃 我会把它拔出来 我只是
going to go with three you could go for
我要买三个你可以买到的
more but I'm just going to go with three
更多 但我只想要三个
and I'm only going to put it on this dut
我只会把它放在这块灰尘上
I'm not going to bother with the others
我不想为其他人费心
I'm going to say this is the special one
我要说这是特别的一次
this is the one that we want your eye to
这就是我们想要你的眼睛
be drawn to so this is the one with a
被吸引 所以这是一个有一个
little bit more detail than the others
比其他的更详细一点
I'm sorry if I'm doing a horrible
如果我做了一件可怕的事 我很抱歉
zigzaggy job of I could do snapping but
我可以做一件曲折的工作 但是
I'm like eh it's just too much work to
我就像 呃 只是工作太多了
the snapping functions for this so I'm
这个的捕捉功能 所以我
going to select those three shift select
我要选择这三个班次选择
the icing contrl p and then go keep
结冰控制 然后继续
transform there we go so now they're all
转变成我们要去的地方所以现在他们都
attached to that just in case I move the
附在上面 以防我移动
donut it's uh it's correctly uh done the
甜甜圈 呃 这是正确的 呃做好了
final thing I think I changed was the
我想我改变的最后一件事是
world settings underneath the air and
空气和空气下的世界环境
dust for our Sky texture I just dialed
我们天空质感的尘埃我刚刚拨打
it back to around about a 7 just a
它回到了大约7摄氏度左右 只是
little bit cooler in the lighting right
灯光更凉爽了一点 对吧
as I might remember I told you if you go
我可能还记得我告诉过你如果你走了
all the way there it's like the sky just
一路上就像天空一样
becomes like blue um and if it's too far
变得像蓝色的 如果太远了
up then it becomes yellow and orange or
然后它会变成黄色和橙色或者
whatever like kind of too decayed but
不管怎么说都太腐朽了 但是
you know like a 7ish it'll just look it
你知道 看起来就像七十出头
just feels a little cleaner um in
只是感觉有点干净 嗯 在
comparison to what it was awesome now
与现在令人惊叹的相比
we're F we're almost there I promise you
我们快到了 我向你保证
we're almost there the one thing that
我们就快到那一件事了
you probably do want to know how to add
您可能确实想知道如何添加
is depth of field it adds a lot because
景深增加了很多 因为
every single camera in the real world
现实世界中的每一台摄像机
has depth of field except for pinhole
除针孔外 具有景深
cameras interestingly because there is
有趣的是摄像机 因为有
no Optics in a pinhole camera so it can
针孔摄像头中没有光学元件 因此它可以
have like infinite depth of field
拥有无限的景深
supposedly um anyways the uh the depth
据推测 嗯 无论如何 嗯 深度
of field settings is underneath your
字段设置位于您的
camera okay so select your camera then
相机好的 那么选择你的相机吧
click on the data here and then depth of
单击此处的数据 然后单击深度
field right at the bottom so check that
字段就在底部 因此请检查
box and everything will become blurry
方框和一切都会变得模糊
because it doesn't have a focus object
因为它没有焦点对象
yet so click the little ey dropper tool
然而 请点击小滴管工具
and then just click on this icing this
然后只需点击这块糖霜
uh pink doughnut icing right in the the
呃粉色的甜甜圈糖衣就在
front here and there you go so that is
前面这里和那里 你走 就是这样
depth of field used to be really
景深过去真的是
difficult to do in blender um I started
很难在搅拌机里做 嗯 我开始
like you know 20 years ago and it was
就像你知道的 20年前
this horrible like motion blow thing you
这个可怕的动作打击了你
had to do for the camera to like rotate
必须要做才能让相机喜欢旋转
it anyway it's it's it's just a checkbox
不管怎么说 这只是一个复选框
now it's it's fascinating anyways uh the
现在它是 无论如何 这很吸引人
f- stop if you're unfamiliar with
如果你不熟悉 就停下来
cameras the lower the F stop the
摄像机的F值越低 将停止
shallower that depth of field so you can
把景深变浅 这样你就可以
see very little of this image is
几乎看不到这张图片
actually in Focus so it's actually good
实际上对焦了 所以这真的很好
for like Miniatures um but if you want
就像微缩作品一样 嗯 但如果你想
more of the scene to be in Focus like
更多的场景需要聚焦 比如
you want more of this donut stack to be
你想让这堆甜甜圈更多
seen I would go with an F stop somewhere
看到我会带着F停靠站去某个地方
between six or eight um you know
六八点之间 嗯 你知道的
something around the range I think I
在范围内的东西我想我
went with eight for my final one or
在我的最后一场比赛中选择了8个人
maybe it was six can't remember anyways
可能是六个人 反正都记不起来了
but you can see the stuff in the
但你可以看到里面的东西
background there is now out of focus and
背景现在是模糊的
it puts the attention where it should be
它把注意力放在了它应该放的地方
right on those donuts in the middle
就在中间的甜甜圈上
there and the other thing that I always
还有另外一件事 我总是
forget to enable is motion blur so
忘记启用是运动模糊 所以
underneath your render settings here uh
在您的渲染设置下面 呃
you just need to check motion blur and I
你只需要检查运动模糊和我
actually find the default setting is
实际上查找的默认设置是
usually fine it's a little smooth like a
通常很好 有点光滑 就像
it's a a little bit too blurry sometimes
有时候有点太模糊了
so you might want to drop it to like 04
所以你可能想把它改成像04
or something but I don't know it should
或者别的什么 但我不知道它应该是什么
be defined with a default it usually
被定义为默认的 它通常
looks okay so are we ready to render our
看起来还行 我们准备好了吗？
final animation well I actually thought
最终动画好吧 我真的以为
yes so that little jump cut that you saw
是的 所以你看到的那个小跳跃剪辑
there was me going yep let's render that
我要去了 是的 让我们来呈现一下
animation and then I rendered it out and
动画 然后我把它渲染出来
then I came back and I went wait a
然后我回来了 我去等了一会儿
minute I've made some
一分钟我就做了一些
errors now can you tell what they are I
错误现在你能说出它们是什么吗？
will give you a
会给你一个
clue right here right here right here
线索就在这里
we're missing those three little balls
我们错过了那三个小球
that we created little sprinkles and
我们创造了一些小点缀和
then also look in the background here
然后再看看这里的背景
mysteriously dark almost as if the area
神秘的黑暗几乎就像是这片区域
lamp that we added is not there so I'll
我们添加的灯不在那里 所以我要
first of all say it's very common to do
首先 说这是很常见的事情
this you think that you're finally ready
这是你认为你终于准备好了
like yeah everything looks good kick off
就像 是的 一切看起来都很好
the final uh animation I've I've
最后一部动画我有
sometimes waited like over a week for a
有时会等上一个多星期
whole animation to finish and then I
完成整个动画 然后我
come back and then I open it up and then
回来 然后我打开它 然后
I go oh no I forgot to turn off that
我走了 哦 不 我忘了关了
layer I forgot to turn on that layer I
层我忘了打开那个层了
forgot you know actually a technique
忘了你其实知道一种技术
that Pixar uses um I learned at one of
皮克斯用的是我在一所
the uh sigraph presentations they did
他们做的那个签名演示文稿
they said they render the first frame
他们说他们渲染了第一帧
the middle frame and the end frame of
的中间框架和结束框架
every shot before they do the full
在他们全力以赴之前的每一次投篮
animation uh sequence uh because that
动画呢序列呢 因为
usually reveals any problems um in the
通常显示任何问题 嗯 在
animation which they can then uh correct
动画 然后他们可以呃纠正
so I should have done that but didn't um
所以我应该这么做的 但是我没有
anyways what was my mistake well when we
不管怎样 我的错误是什么呢
uh disabled this sprinkles collection
Uh禁用了这款Sinkles收藏
right we disabled it from appearing in
对 我们禁止它出现在
the render that's fine but when we
渲染这很好 但当我们
created these objects I didn't check
创建了这些我没有检查的对象
what was the active collection so when
当时活跃的藏品是什么？
you add a new object it adds it to
您添加一个新对象 它会将其添加到
whatever is the selected collection this
无论这是什么选定的集合
little one with the little uh box around
拿着那个小盒子的小个子
it so obviously it put it inside of that
很明显 它把它放在里面
collection so these spheres should not
集合 因此这些球体不应该
be inside the sprinkles so I'm going to
在喷泉里 所以我要去
drag it out into a duts uh collection
把它拖到DUTS 呃 收藏中
which is where it should be and then
这是它应该在的地方 然后
this area lamp as well that's the reason
这个区域灯也是 这就是原因
that the uh the background is dark um is
那个呃背景是暗的这个是
cuz that was inside the sprinkle so it
因为它就在喷头里面 所以它
was hidden from the rendler as well so
对兰德勒来说也是如此
now putting that into the environment
现在把它放到环境中
that now should look a lot better so do
现在看起来应该好多了 确实如此
a test render just by hitting F12 see
只需按F12即可进行测试渲染(请参阅
how that looks first what I should have
这看起来是什么样子 我首先应该有什么
done I mean even just doing one render
完成了 我的意思是即使只做一次渲染
could have revealed this problem it's
可能会暴露出这个问题
that obvious um but do a test render
这很明显 嗯 但要进行测试渲染
check look we've got the balls appearing
检查 看 我们有球出现了
The Fill light is now in the background
填充灯光现在位于背景中
and the other thing I noticed and this
我注意到的另一件事是
is because it's the next day that I'm
是因为就在第二天我
recording this um when you look at
录制这个 当你看的时候
something with fresh eyes you often
一些你经常看到的新鲜的东西
notice different things so I thought
注意到不同的东西 所以我想
that this exposure looked pretty good
这次曝光看起来很不错
but then now having a look at it um the
但是现在看一看 嗯
next day I can see that it's a little
第二天我就能看出来它有一点
Overexposed okay so if you look uh at
过度曝光好的 所以如果你看 呃
the false color this is what it looks
假颜色这就是它看起来的样子
like and there's just too much orange
就像有太多的橙色
there so essentially I'm going to drop
所以从本质上讲 我要放弃
this back to be so it's like mostly
这回是这样的 好像大部分时间
yellow across the uh the front of these
黄色穿过 呃 这些的前面
Donuts here well not mostly yellow but
这里的甜甜圈不是大部分是黄色的 但
more yellow than what there was uh
比以前更黄了 呃
before there's not really an exact way
在没有确切的方法之前
to sort of uh pinpoint it but I could
想要找到它 但是我可以
just tell it's a little Overexposed so
告诉我它有点过度曝光了 所以
I'm just dialing it back to be a little
我只是把它拨回来 让它有点
more reasonable again your exposure
你的风险敞口再次变得更合理
ranges might be different depending on
范围可能会有所不同 具体取决于
you know how close your Donuts are to
你知道你的甜甜圈离
the window or something but look at it
窗户之类的 但你看看它
with your own eyes and if it looks wrong
用你自己的眼睛 如果看起来不对
when you're using this exposure range
当你使用这个曝光范围时
use a different value tweak it and try
使用不同的值调整它 然后尝试
to make it um look accurate cuz actually
为了让它看起来很准确 因为实际上
I was on Discord this morning looking at
我今天早上在不和频道上看着
some of your renders join the Discord if
在以下情况下 您的一些渲染会加入不和谐
you're not on there um and I was like
你不在上面 嗯 我就像
okay a lot of people also have
好的 很多人也有
Overexposed uh renders so I should bring
过度曝光 呃渲染 所以我应该带
that up anyway we are now finally ready
不管怎样 我们现在终于准备好了
to do a render so again I am using no
为了再次进行渲染 我使用no
noise threshold 500 samples probably get
噪声阈值500个样本可能会
that up to a th000 if you want it to be
如果你想的话 最高可达10000美元
non- jittery D noise open image D noise
无抖动D噪声开放图像D噪声
and then I'm outputting it to tiffs just
然后我把它输出给TIFF
RGB we don't need alpha 8 bit and then
RGB我们不需要阿尔法8位 然后
I'm just putting it into a folder which
我只是把它放在一个文件夹里
because I made a mistake uh I'm going to
因为我犯了个错误 呃 我要
put it into another F actually made two
换成另一个F实际上等于两个
mistakes rendered it
错误地呈现了它
twice I'll put it into uh three right
两次 我会把它放进 呃 三 对
that's why I put them in sub folders
这就是我把它们放入子文件夹的原因
anyways now that I'm ready I'm going to
不管怎样 现在我准备好了 我要
go render render animation and this is
去渲染渲染动画 这是
now kicking it off I can now leave it
现在开始 我现在可以离开它了
walk away and it will just start as it
走开 一切都会开始的
finishes uh rendering it'll just start
完成渲染后 它才刚刚开始
dumping it into the folder and there you
将其转储到文件夹中 然后您就可以
go so you can see it's uh it's rendered
去吧 这样你就能看到它 呃 它被渲染了
three frames so we've got three images
三帧 所以我们有三幅图像
here once it's finished we should have
在这里 一旦完工 我们就应该
160 Tiff files inside this folder which
此文件夹中的160个Tiff文件
you will have to watch the final part of
你将不得不观看最后一集
this tutorial to learn how to take that
这篇教程是为了学习如何利用
sequence and form a video file that you
对视频文件进行排序并形成视频文件
can use and send Etc so click here to
可以使用和发送等 因此请单击此处
watch the final part of this tutorial
观看本教程的最后部分
series
系列